Now,
you're probably crippled as a content
pussy by a fear of judgment.
You are not worried about what your
clients think.
You're worried about what other people in
your industry think.
As an accountant talking about corp tax,
you're wondering what other accountants
will think. As a chef putting out recipes,
you're worried what other chefs will
think. As a personal trainer, as a coach,
you're worried about what other coaches
will think. They are the only people
that will never buy your shit.
That's like being a fucking butchers
and worrying what the vegans are thinking.
Do you understand how moronic it
is to be feared to be judged by peers?
Literally the only people
that will never buy your shit.
And if you want to get over the fear of
anything, action is a fucking amazing way
to do it. So what I mean by that, in CBT,
cognitive behavioral therapy, I'm
pretty sure there's something called
exposure therapy.
So if you're scared of something,
you should expose yourself to it.
Now, if you're scared of spiders,
don't go jump in a pit full of a million
fucking
huntsman spiders. Not that.
But you could find a really small,
non-scary
spider and hold it in your hand for a
minute. And guess what?
It would help you be less scared of
spiders.
If you hate public speaking,
you could do some public speaking to a
crowd of 10
people, do some volunteer work,
whatever it is.
If you're afraid of asking out girls for
their number, you could start
complimenting females when you're out
and about and just saying, "Hey,
I like your
shoes." There are ways
that you can break down the fears of
anything you have by
just getting more exposure to it.
If you're scared of posting content,
where do you
think the remedy is to getting better at
that? Posting more content.
The only way to get over fear of judgment
is to put out fucking loads of content.
And if you think there's any way around
that, you're a fucking cretin